Hello friends, today we will talk
about ICI Lumbard General Insurance Company stocks. Today, this stock has
made a high and broken out.
We will try to understand the reason behind the volume trading seen in this stock today.
If you are
new to watching our videos, then definitely subscribe to our channel.
If you like our channel
through videos, then
this video is going to be special for those who work in intraday. Because I am going to
specifically tell you when to book profit in intraday.
Without target and without support,
today I am going to teach you a method
which no one has explained to you yet. So
let's start the video.
First of all, we will
try to understand why this stock
saw the highest volume today and why this stock
gave a breakout. This stock was
shown on TV news channels today and in the
morning, a buy position was indicated in this stock on
ICI Lumbard General Insurance
Company. So the volume generated here was the
first  The reason here is that
if a stroke is shown on TV, then the
volume in that stock definitely increases, whether it
increases or decreases. It does not matter whether the stock increases or
decreases. If
once the TV news channel
announces any stock, then small retail
investors definitely buy or
sell it. Targets are also mentioned in it.
If you watch that video
in the morning or you watch
CNBC Awaaz Morning, you will find it,
you can go and check it out.
Secondly, this stock was trading near its high, in
which the TV news channel people had
announced its high. Also, a
very big deal was done with it
regarding ICI Lumbard, due to which
this stock was showing a very good
profit for us and everyone must have made a lot of money
in this stock.
Perhaps the upward movement in the stock
started from the opening of the market and many people must have made a lot of money. The
first target in the stock,
you can see, was around the high of this channel,
which  Our level here
was approximately 734.35 and as soon as this level broke out in the stock, the
target after that was 1747 and
after that you will not know
when and how to take the target of the stock. Friends,
everyone will tell you the old target by
looking at the chart. It is in everyone's power to
look at the chart and
tell the levels of the stock by looking at the high level. So this was the
old level of the stock, this was
1747. The stock also broke out of this level
but the stock has again
given a closing on the downside. Definitely there was a
slight decline in the stock and it is possible
that more declines may be seen. So now the
support level that will be formed for your stock will be formed
here around the high of this candle
which is almost formed here at
1660. Definitely the support level of the stock can be
formed here. I am going to tell you the reason here,
listen to this also carefully,
if you know then the stock was
trading repeatedly at this high level here and the stock
declined and  The stock broke this low and
made a low here. Now our stock is
trading at an all-time high and
along with the stock moving high, if the stock is to continue the uptrend, then it is
definitely
very important for the stock to make a low above the last low of this level. If
our stock breaks this level, there will be a fall.
Therefore, if we want to follow the uptrend, then it is
very important to make a low above this low, which is
₹1,111. And then the strong support level,
this high level of ours is visible
through support, so this level can
become a support for you, which I have told you about,
and the last stop loss which you will have to
keep is ₹1,111. Whenever the stock
makes a high and when it finds a downward move, then
take a stop loss of the last low
because if our stock breaks that level, then there will
definitely be a fall. Now we will
talk here about when and how you had to
book profit, so I am going to explain that thing to you in a very simple way,
so now we will move on to the 15-minute
chart pattern.  Because
people have to take profit in intraday only, now how to
take it, I am telling you in this video,
so listen carefully,
if you see here, this was our
latest high of the stock, okay, like the stock
opened in the morning, the stock
broke out of this high level,
after breaking out above it, it gave closing, so now
you had got the chance here that
our stock will be seen going up from here, now
what you had to do was that this candle of
15 minutes was formed, after this you will see, three of our
candles are formed here, two green and one
red candle, so till our stock makes a high, you will
see, the stock made a high here, then it
made a high in this also, it made a high in this also, all the
three candles made a high, then the stock made a
fourth candle high, then a green candle
closed near the high, then the stock made a high, then the stock made a
green candle, then the stock made a high, then the
stock made a
high and made a green canal, after that you
will see, the high of this canal is ₹1 6695 paisa, the
second canal did not make a high, ₹1  A
high of 6625 paise was made, after that you will see that the
stock made a red canal and the
closing is also near the low, so this was the candle where
you had to book your profit or
you had to be alert that
if our next candle again breaks the low of this candle
and closes below it and does
not break out the high of this canal,
then you could have booked your profit,
so you had to book your profit around this candle
which is approximately our
level here 1754, 50 or 55,
you would have got profit here, after that you will see that the
stock made a low, then the stock broke this low
and after going up, the stock
could not break out this low, then the stock
declined and by adding this low, a low was made here,
now the stock is again coming down, so
obviously the stock will definitely
take support and for taking support, the
chart pattern of 15 mits is the high of this candle which is
₹10, so now this will be seen becoming your support level,
along with this I have made a major  I have
told you the support level, I hope
you have understood this video of mine well
and if you have understood the story that I have explained to you from here till
here
well, then it is a good
thing, please do tell us by commenting what
you understood, so let's
pause the video, thank you, see you in the new video.